Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1932-2004; XVIII.
  - Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; 11.
    - International Photographs
      - Vargus, General, Colombian National Police (4), September 19, 1990 (Box 1539, Folder 32)
      - Vasquez, Gaddi, Uruguay--Drop-By Visit (3), April 2, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 1)
      - Vassalli, Italian Minister of Justice (2), September 15, 1988 (Box 1540, Folder 2)
      - Waddington, David, British Home Secretary--Meeting (3), February 12, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 3)
      - Wathelet, Melchoir, Belgian Vice Prime Minister (3), February 20, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 4)
      - Webster, William, Director of CIA (1), March 5, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 5)
      - Wilkey, Ambassador Malcolm, OAG Reception (5), May 17, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 6)
      - Wilkins, Howard, U.S. Ambassador to the Netherlands (2), December 12, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 7)
      - Yakovlev, Soviet Justice Minister (2), August 15, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 8)
      - Zappala, Joseph, U.S. Ambassador to Spain (1), April 17, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 9)
      - Zaslavski, Ilya, Soviet People's Congress (3), September 6, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 10)
      - Zhelev, Zhelyu, President of Bulgaria (8), September 26, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 11)
    - Press Photographs
      - ABC News, Carole Kabrin and Tim O'Brien--Presentation of Kabrin's Sketch made at the Payne Supreme Court Case (3), June 14, 1991 (Box 1540, Folder 12)
      - Asset Forfeiture Announcement in Houston with Senator Phil Gramm (3), November 17, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 13)
      - Asset Forfeiture Announcement, in Prince George's County (5), March 29, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 14)
      - Business-Higher Education Forum Press Availability (4), June 25 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 15)
      - CBS--Face the Nation--Thornburgh Named AG (1), August 14, 1988 (Box 1540, Folder 16)
      - CBS--Face the Nation (1), July, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 17)
      - Crime Package Press Conference with the AGAC (3), May 23, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 18)
      - Justice Inaugural Symposium (6), September 17, 1990 (Box 1540, Folder 19)
      - NBC--Meet the Press (2), September 11, 1988 (Box 1540, Folder 20)
      - NBC--Meet the Press (2), January 22, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 21)
      - NBC--Meet the Press (1), August 20, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 22)
      - NBC--Meet the Press (1), June 30, 1991 (Box 1540, Folder 23)
      - Nationwide Report on Drug Trafficking Press Conference (3), August 3, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 24)
      - Radio America with John Angelus (2), September 19, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 25)
      - U.S. Marshal Press Conference on Operation STOP with Bennett and Morris (2), July 17, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 26)
      - White Collar Crime News Conference with Ed Dennis and Rudy Giuliani (3), January 31, 1989 (Box 1540, Folder 27)
    - Event Albums
      - Office of Attorney General Christmas Party Album (101), December, 1988 (Box 1541, Folder 1)
      - Quantico Visit Album (132), July 19, 1989 (Box 1541, Folder 2)
      - 200th Anniversary, Office of the Attorney General (156), September 22, 1989 (Box 1541, Folder 3)
      - Soviet Union Trip, Album 1 (141), October, 1989 (Box 1542, Folder 1)
      - Soviet Union Trip, Album 2 (239), October, 1989 (Box 1542, Folder 2)
      - Soviet Union Trip, Gift Album (30), October, 1989 (Box 1542, Folder 3)
      - Office of Attorney General Christmas Party, Album 1 (72), December 19, 1989 (Box 1543, Folder 1)
      - Office of Attorney General Christmas Party, Album 2 (108), December 19, 1989 (Box 1543, Folder 2)
      - University of Scranton Commencement (10), May 26, 1990 (Box 1543, Folder 3)
      - U.S. Mexico Attorneys General Border Conference Album, Sante Fe, NM (10), May, 1990 (Box 1544, Folder 1)
      - Soviet Delegation to the U.S. Album 1 (227), August, 1990 (Box 1544, Folder 2)
      - Soviet Delegation to the U.S. Album 2 (208), August, 1990 (Box 1545, Folder 1)
      - 2nd Conference of Attorneys General of the Asia-Pacific Region, Seoul, Korea, Album (56), September 3-6, 1990 (Box 1545, Folder 2)
      - Midby-Byron Distinguished Leadership Award Honoring Dick Thornburgh, Album (66), November 9, 1990 (Box 1546, Folder 1)
      - Bulgaria Trip (47), December, 1990 ? (Box 1546, Folder 2)
      - Minister of Justice of the Russian Republic, Nikolai Fyodorov, Album (120), March 8, 1991 (Box 1546, Folder 3)
      - William French Smith Memorial Tribute, Great Hall, Album (74), April 19, 1991 (Box 1547, Folder 1)
      - Points of Light Ceremony Album (80), April 26, 1991 (Box 1547, Folder 2)
      - Operation PAR Album (38), May, 1991 (Box 1547, Folder 3)
      - American Disabilities Act One Year Anniversary Album and photographs of ribbon-cutting for Great Hall ramp, July 26, 1991 (Box 1548, Folder 1)
      - Speaking to disability advocates after the signing of the Americans with Disabilities Act, July 26, 1990 (Box 1548, Folder 2)
      - American Disabilities Act One Year Anniversary Album (136), July 26, 1991 (Box 1548, Folder 3)
      - Farewell Ceremony Honoring Attorney General Dick Thornburgh, Album 1 (90), August 15, 1991 (Box 1548, Folder 4)
      - Farewell Ceremony Honoring Attorney General Dick Thornburgh, Album 2 (93), August 15, 1991 (Box 1548, Folder 5)
  - Campaign for United States Senate, 1991; 12.
    - Harris Wofford, undated (Box 1549, Folder 1)
    - Announcement to run for Senate, Philadelphia, PA, undated (Box 1549, Folder 2)
    - Shrine of Czestochowa, Bucks County, PA (1), September 3, 1991 (Box 1549, Folder 3)
    - Philadelphia Fundraiser (5), September 12, 1991 (Box 1549, Folder 4)
    - President Bush with Dick and Ginny Thornburgh at Campaign Fundraiser, Pittsburgh (2) (Box 1549, Folder 5)
    - Thornburgh and President Bush on Air Force 1 (2), October 2, 1991 (Box 1549, Folder 6)
    - Campaigning with First Lady Barbara Bush at a Philadelphia School (6), October 17, 1991 (Box 1549, Folder 7)
    - Scranton Rally (3), November 3, 1991 (Box 1549, Folder 8)
    - Ginny Thornburgh at Meridian Bank Event, January 21, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Photographs, 1991-1992 (Box 1549, Folder 10)
  - United Nations, 1993; 13.
    - Portrait of Dick Thornburgh, Under-Secretary-General for Administration and Management, United Nations (1), March 26, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 11)
    - Secretary General Boutros Boutros-Ghali's Visit to Washington, DC: Luncheon at the White House (1), May 12, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 12)
    - Hastings Law School Event for Former Attorneys General (3), June 14, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 13)
    - With Alan Reich, Harold Wilke, and Boutros Boutros-Ghali at Disabilities Luncheon (1), July 9, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 14)
    - Somalia Refugee Camp, Kenya, August, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 15)
    - American Legion Distinguished Service Medal Award for "Outstanding Service to the Community, State, and Nation," Chicago, IL (8), August 26, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 16)
    - Yale University Forum on the UN, New Haven, CT (1), October 31, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 17)
    - 7th International Conference: Disabled Persons in Society, the Vatican, November 19-21, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 18)
    - Russia Trip (10), November, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Society Dinner, New York, NY, December 12, 1992 (Box 1549, Folder 20)
    - Luncheon in honor of President George Bush, Washington, DC (1), January 12, 1993 (Box 1549, Folder 21)
    - Visit to United States Department of Justice, DEA (2), January 19, 1993 (Box 1549, Folder 22)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh, 1993 (Box 1549, Folder 23)
    - Lunch at the UN (1), undated (Box 1549, Folder 24)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (2), undated (Box 1549, Folder 25)
    - People at the UN, undated (Box 1549, Folder 26)
  - Ongoing Career, 14.
    - Gore, Al, June 26, 1993 (Box 1549, Folder 27)
    - Pendelphia Foundation, October 20, 1993 (Box 1549, Folder 28)
    - Trip to Russia to Monitor Elections (17), December, 1993 (Box 1549, Folder 29)
    - ARC Allegheny, Ginny and Peter Thornburgh and Virginia Judson (1), March, 1994 (Box 1549, Folder 30)
    - Commencement at Shippensburg University (3), May 7, 1994 (Box 1549, Folder 31)
    - Trip to Hong Kong (8), June, 1994 (Box 1549, Folder 32)
    - Dedication Day at Dixon University Center of the State System of Higher Education, Harrisburg, PA (1), October 20, 1994 (Box 1549, Folder 33)
    - Trip to Guatemala (10), 1994-1995 (Box 1549, Folder 34)
    - Dick and Ginny Thornburgh at Governor Tom Ridge's Inaugural Ceremony (1), January 17, 1995 (Box 1549, Folder 35)
    - Cumberland School of Law, Birmingham, AL (11), March 14, 1995 (Box 1549, Folder 36)
    - Dr. Dai-Chul Chung's Visit to Washington (2), May, 1995 (Box 1549, Folder 37)
    - Defiance College Commencement, Defiance, OH (5), May 7, 1995 (Box 1549, Folder 38)
    - "That All May Worship," Korea (4), June, 1995 (Box 1550, Folder 1)
    - Trip to Korea, Album (18), June 15, 1995 (Box 1550, Folder 2)
    - California District Attorneys Association, Summer Conference, Lake Tahoe (1), June 27, 1995 (Box 1550, Folder 3)
    - Visit with Russian Chief Judge Yakovlev, Washington, DC (4), October, 1995 (Box 1550, Folder 4)
    - Event with Elsie Hillman (1), 1997 (Box 1550, Folder 5)
    - ARCO Chemical Groundbreaking in France, On-Board the Azur (2), 1998 (Box 1550, Folder 6)
    - Hong Kong (3), March, 1998 (Box 1550, Folder 7)
    - 6th International Conference on Rehabilitation of People with Disabilities, Korea (10), July, 1998 (Box 1550, Folder 8)
    - Formal Portrait (1), 1999 (Box 1550, Folder 9)
    - Hong Kong (9), 1999 (Box 1550, Folder 10)
    - Richmond Lawyers Chapter of the Federalist Society, Richmond, VA, June 29, 1999 (Box 1550, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Opera's Maecenas XVI Gala "Tito e Gigi's Last Tango in Pittsburgh" (1), May 20, 2000 (Box 1550, Folder 12)
    - Vacationing in Maine, 2001 (Box 1550, Folder 13)
    - Yale Friend Reunion, Washington, DC (1), Spring, 2001 (Box 1550, Folder 14)
    - Family Reunion, Pennsylvania, Summer 2001 (Box 1550, Folder 15)
    - NDI Pre-Election Mission to Cambodia, January 27-February 4, 2003 (Box 1550, Folder 16)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary Trip to Paris and Switzerland, April 22-May 5, 2003 (Box 1550, Folder 17)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) 25th Anniversary Symposium, Smithsonian Institute, Museum of American History, Washington, DC (10), March 28, 2004 (Box 1550, Folder 18)
    - OJ Simpson Trial, 1995 (Box 1550, Folder 19)
    - IRI Election Monitoring, Russia, 1996 (Box 1550, Folder 20)
    - Presentation of Thornburgh Papers to University of Pittsburgh, Nordenberg and Thornburgh, and others, February 7, 1998 (Box 1550, Folder 21)
    - IRI Presidential Election Monitoring, Ukraine, November, 1999 (Box 1550, Folder 22)
    - NDI Governors Forum, Nigeria, April, 1999 (Box 1550, Folder 23)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary trip to Holy Land, March-April, 2000 (Box 1550, Folder 24)
    - AAPD gives Betts Award to Dick and Ginny Thornburgh, Introduction by Peter Thornburgh, March 14, 2003 (Box 1550, Folder 25)
    - Thormburgh Family Disability Lectureship: Judy Heumann speaker, February 9, 2006 (Box 1550, Folder 26)